adifferentleague.co.uk 2012-05-12

# Privacy and Terms

### Introduction

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.adifferentleague.co.uk. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We, A Different League, are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to and collect information that you voluntarily give us, by email or by other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use the information you give us to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about future events or changes to this privacy policy.

Cookies and other Technology

This website does use cookies as a method of collecting website statistics. This information cannot be used to identify any individual and only last as long as your visit.

Security 

The Department takes precautions to protect the information about you. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers and servers which store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that A Different League is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, they read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

Contact

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately at info@adifferentlegaue.co.uk
